You can receive a lot of awards in your life but there is nothing better nothing better than being honored by your own.
My philosophy is that not only are you responsible for your life but doing the best at this moment puts you in the best place for the next moment.
I believe that one of life's greatest risks is never daring to risk.
Be thankful for what you have; you'll end up having more. If you concentrate on what you don't have you will never ever have enough.
I think that when you invite people to your home you invite them to yourself.
Do the one thing you think you cannot do. Fail at it. Try again. Do better the second time. The only people who never tumble are those who never mount the high wire. This is your moment. Own it.
Real integrity is doing the right thing knowing that nobody's going to know whether you did it or not.
The big secret in life is that there is no big secret. Whatever your goal you can get there if you're willing to work.
Every day brings a chance for you to draw in a breath kick off your shoes and dance.
As you become more clear about who you really are you'll be better able to decide what is best for you - the first time around.
Shine within you so that it can shine on someone else. Let your light shine.
I've come to believe that each of us has a personal calling that's as unique as a fingerprint - and that the best way to succeed is to discover what you love and then find a way to offer it to others in the form of service working hard and also allowing the energy of the universe to lead you.
I don't think you ever stop giving. I really don't. I think it's an on-going process. And it's not just about being able to write a check. It's being able to touch somebody's life.
Unless you choose to do great things with it it makes no difference how much you are rewarded or how much power you have.
Every time you state what you want or believe you're the first to hear it. It's a message to both you and others about what you think is possible. Don't put a ceiling on yourself.
For everyone of us that succeeds it's because there's somebody there to show you the way out. The light doesn't always necessarily have to be in your family; for me it was teachers and school.
What I know for sure is that what you give comes back to you.
Every one of us gets through the tough times because somebody is there standing in the gap to close it for us.
With every experience you alone are painting your own canvas thought by thought choice by choice.
I believe the choice to be excellent begins with aligning your thoughts and words with the intention to require more from yourself.
Breathe. Let go. And remind yourself that this very moment is the only one you know you have for sure.
It took a lot of courage to take the high road but I would rather be significant with six million people watching a show with meaning than everyone watching a show with no meaning.
You know you are on the road to success if you would do your job and not be paid for it.
You can have it all. You just can't have it all at once.
If you neglect to recharge a battery it dies. And if you run full speed ahead without stopping for water you lose momentum to finish the race.
The key to realizing a dream is to focus not on success but significance - and then even the small steps and little victories along your path will take on greater meaning.
We are each responsible for our own life - no other person is or even can be.
What I know is is that if you do work that you love and the work fulfills you the rest will come.
The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the life of your dreams.
Lots of people want to ride with you in the limo but what you want is someone who will take the bus with you when the limo breaks down.
Living in the moment brings you a sense of reverence for all of life's blessings.
I believe that every single event in life happens in an opportunity to choose love over fear.
Whatever you fear most has no power - it is your fear that has the power.
Energy is the essence of life. Every day you decide how you're going to use it by knowing what you want and what it takes to reach that goal and by maintaining focus.
Though I am grateful for the blessings of wealth it hasn't changed who I am. My feet are still on the ground. I'm just wearing better shoes.
I trust that everything happens for a reason even when we're not wise enough to see it.
Challenges are gifts that force us to search for a new center of gravity. Don't fight them. Just find a different way to stand.
Think like a queen. A queen is not afraid to fail. Failure is another steppingstone to greatness.
The more you praise and celebrate your life the more there is in life to celebrate.
What God intended for you goes far beyond anything you can imagine.
Devote today to something so daring even you can’t believe you’re doing it.